Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is colorful and bright
Truth and lies confuse our sight
Use your heart to look and find
The truth is close, not far behind
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies
Can't escape this gray smoke inside
Bring all your courage to the fight
Maybe you can save the world tonight
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Forgot your spine
What are feelings?
Why?
Why can't they be mass-produced?
After six months of combat testing,
The 3000 series is stable across the board.
It's perfectly ready for mass production.
Especially with self-learning ability
And high-end electromagnetic weapons —
The perfect 3000A model.
It can truly be described as "perfect."
I also strongly agree with mass-producing humanoid machines.
But the public still has plenty of objections
So I've decided
to send the most outstanding unit, 3000A
on a solo mission of great importance
to change how the public views the 3000 series
Recently, the second-in-command of the Gold Tooth Gang,
Hawking, who escaped during the harbor incident
secretly contacted the Security Department yesterday
and is willing to become a witness for the prosecution
to help capture the Gold Tooth Gang's top leader, Heidi
You must guarantee
the safety of the witness, Hawking
I am the most perfect
I will complete this mission perfectly
Of course they sent you
Please, you have to protect my son!
Where is Heidi?
If I weren't afraid Heidi would hurt my son,
I'd never do something so treacherous
Where is Heidi?
Where is he?!
Strange
He was right here a second ago
Dad!
Hawking
You traitor!
Put my son down now!
Today, either I
shoot your son dead,
or you help me
get rid of this annoying robot.
The choice is yours.
You dare hesitate?
Watch me shoot him now!
No!
Let him go!
Come with me.
Little robot,
you underestimate me too much.
You recognize this, right?
You actually kept it hidden on you?
I knew you'd find this place,
so I kept it on me all along.
Back off!
Now, one light tap on this ore
and this kid goes down with me.
Hawxing!
Your Security Department wouldn't ignore a hostage's life, right?
Shut up.
Robot.
I advise you to stop being so relentless.
Let's both give a little ground.
It's good for both of us.
Final warning.
Drop your weapon.
Accept legal punishment.
Heidi might be
carrying a radioactive weapon of mass destruction.
If there are special circumstances,
shoot him dead on the spot.
Bastard.
Aren't you afraid I'll take action?
Don't push me.
You dare—
I'll go back with you.
Stop pressuring Heidi.
Harming my son.
I must complete the mission perfectly.
You—Don't force me.
Dad.
Come back! Don't think you can escape.
Don't move.
Cannot auto-defend.
Hawxing!
Run!
You must come with me right now
Let go of me
My mission is only to save you
Hawxing
Dad
None of you are getting away!
Let's all go down together!
Hawxing
Dad
Please return to the Security Department with me
You... you
emotionless monster!
This is outrageous!
Why didn't Unit 3000A rescue the hostage?
Why did Hawking's son die?
Isn't Unit 3000A supposed to be perfect? Huh?
But the mission instructions didn't mention Hawking's son
Unit 3000A was only following orders
The most perfect humanoid machine doesn't even have that basic common sense?
How could we mass-produce a machine with no feelings like that?
Chief, we've got a problem!
Unit 3000A suddenly activated while unloading weapons
He's getting away!
Capture him now!
3000A
You're surrounded!
Resistance is futile!
Surrender now!
Face the Security Department's judgment!
I am the most perfect!
Dad!
Hawxing!
You... emotionless monster!
I am the most perfect!
I completed my mission perfectly!
But... what are feelings?
Is 3000A really disarmed?
Of course. He's just an ordinary robot now.
Don't be afraid!
Move in!
3000A was never disarmed!
He's still fully armed!
The strongest humanoid machine!
We don't stand a chance!
Leave this to us!
3000B 3000C
That's incredible!
Wrapped up so fast!
3000B 3000C, incredible!
Mission complete. Fall back!
I am perfection itself.
I completed my mission flawlessly.
But what are emotions?
[Special Ending Theme]
MojoSpy Discord: https://discord.gg/BkdRezCkxf